{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n12x^2 - 24x + 12 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-6x + 6 and -2x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-6x + 6\u003d 0\n-2x + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n12x^2 - 24x + 18 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-7x^2 - 56x + 63 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 9 and 7x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 9\u003d 0\n7x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-7x^2 - 56x + 66 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 7x - 12 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 4 and x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 4\u003d 0\nx - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 7x - 3 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 - 12x - 10 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 5 and 2x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 5\u003d 0\n2x + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 - 12x - 6 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n27x^2 - 27 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-9x - 9 and -3x + 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-9x - 9\u003d 0\n-3x + 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n27x^2 - 25 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 5", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n-3x^2 + 24x - 45 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x + 9 and x - 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x + 9\u003d 0\nx - 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-3x^2 + 24x - 38 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -3", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 4x + 21 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 7 and x + 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 7\u003d 0\nx + 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 4x + 30 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, 5", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n7x^2 - 42x + 35 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-7x + 7 and -x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-7x + 7\u003d 0\n-x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n7x^2 - 42x + 44 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n18x^2 - 36x + 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n9x - 9 and 2x - 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n9x - 9\u003d 0\n2x - 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n18x^2 - 36x + 27 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, 4", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 + 8x + 32 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x - 4 and 2x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x - 4\u003d 0\n2x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 + 8x + 40 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-8x^2 + 16x + 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x - 8 and x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x - 8\u003d 0\nx - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-8x^2 + 16x + 27 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n-32x^2 - 96x - 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n8x + 8 and -4x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n8x + 8\u003d 0\n-4x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-32x^2 - 96x - 56 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 - 12x - 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 6 and -3x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 6\u003d 0\n-3x - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 - 12x - 14 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-9x^2 + 27x - 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x + 6 and 3x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x + 6\u003d 0\n3x - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-9x^2 + 27x - 14 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-8x^2 - 40x + 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx + 6 and -8x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx + 6\u003d 0\n-8x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-8x^2 - 40x + 49 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 7", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n3x^2 - 30x + 63 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x - 9 and x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x - 9\u003d 0\nx - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n3x^2 - 30x + 65 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n-28x^2 - 28x + 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x + 8 and -7x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x + 8\u003d 0\n-7x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-28x^2 - 28x + 62 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n36x^2 + 72x + 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n9x + 9 and 4x + 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n9x + 9\u003d 0\n4x + 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n36x^2 + 72x + 44 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-6x^2 - 6x + 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x - 8 and 3x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x - 8\u003d 0\n3x - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-6x^2 - 6x + 77 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-32x^2 - 96x - 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-4x - 8 and 8x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-4x - 8\u003d 0\n8x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-32x^2 - 96x - 61 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n7x^2 - 7 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-7x + 7 and -x - 1\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-7x + 7\u003d 0\n-x - 1 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n7x^2 - 2 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4, 7", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 + 6x + 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x + 8 and -x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x + 8\u003d 0\n-x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 + 6x + 64 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n40x^2 - 80x + 40 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x + 8 and -5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x + 8\u003d 0\n-5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n40x^2 - 80x + 46 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n36x^2 - 36x - 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-9x - 9 and -4x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-9x - 9\u003d 0\n-4x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n36x^2 - 36x - 68 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-10x^2 + 10x + 20 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-5x - 5 and 2x - 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-5x - 5\u003d 0\n2x - 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-10x^2 + 10x + 29 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n9x^2 + 45x - 54 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 6 and -9x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 6\u003d 0\n-9x + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n9x^2 + 45x - 48 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -8", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 - 36x - 32 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x + 4 and -x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x + 4\u003d 0\n-x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 - 36x - 30 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-7x^2 - 49x + 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 8 and 7x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 8\u003d 0\n7x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-7x^2 - 49x + 58 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n18x^2 - 72x + 54 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x - 6 and 9x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x - 6\u003d 0\n9x - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n18x^2 - 72x + 58 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, 6", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n8x^2 - 56x + 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x + 8 and -x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x + 8\u003d 0\n-x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n8x^2 - 56x + 51 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n5x^2 - 5 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 1 and -5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 1\u003d 0\n-5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n5x^2 - 2 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7, 4", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\nx^2 + 3x - 28 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 7 and -x + 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 7\u003d 0\n-x + 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\nx^2 + 3x - 21 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n28x^2 - 84x + 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-4x + 8 and -7x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-4x + 8\u003d 0\n-7x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n28x^2 - 84x + 62 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-12x^2 - 48x - 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x - 6 and 6x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x - 6\u003d 0\n6x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-12x^2 - 48x - 27 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n-12x^2 - 48x - 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x + 6 and -6x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x + 6\u003d 0\n-6x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-12x^2 - 48x - 29 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n18x^2 + 18x - 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x + 4 and 9x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x + 4\u003d 0\n9x - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n18x^2 + 18x - 29 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 - 16x - 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx + 6 and -2x - 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx + 6\u003d 0\n-2x - 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 - 16x - 19 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-8x^2 + 64x + 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 9 and 8x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 9\u003d 0\n8x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-8x^2 + 64x + 81 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-15x^2 - 30x - 15 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x - 3 and 5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x - 3\u003d 0\n5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-15x^2 - 30x - 10 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 6 and -x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 6\u003d 0\n-x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 37 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, 7", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n2x^2 - 16x + 14 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 2 and -x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 2\u003d 0\n-x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n2x^2 - 16x + 17 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -8", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-3x^2 - 18x + 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x - 6 and -x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x - 6\u003d 0\n-x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-3x^2 - 18x + 57 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-7x^2 - 49x - 42 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 6 and 7x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 6\u003d 0\n7x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-7x^2 - 49x - 37 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -4", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\nx^2 + 7x + 12 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 3 and -x - 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 3\u003d 0\n-x - 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\nx^2 + 7x + 13 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-36x^2 + 72x - 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x - 4 and -9x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x - 4\u003d 0\n-9x + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-36x^2 + 72x - 35 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n3x^2 + 18x - 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 8 and -3x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 8\u003d 0\n-3x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n3x^2 + 18x - 47 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 9", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-5x^2 + 40x + 45 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-5x - 5 and x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-5x - 5\u003d 0\nx - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-5x^2 + 40x + 46 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4, 8", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 + 8x + 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x - 8 and x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x - 8\u003d 0\nx - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 + 8x + 65 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 - 12x - 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x - 3 and -2x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x - 3\u003d 0\n-2x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 - 12x - 9 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 - 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x + 6 and -2x - 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x + 6\u003d 0\n-2x - 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 - 20 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n9x^2 + 9x - 54 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x + 9 and 3x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x + 9\u003d 0\n3x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n9x^2 + 9x - 53 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-8x^2 + 16x - 8 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x - 4 and -2x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x - 4\u003d 0\n-2x + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-8x^2 + 16x + 1 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-10x^2 + 10 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 2 and 5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 2\u003d 0\n5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-10x^2 + 12 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n2x^2 - 6x + 4 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 1 and 2x - 4\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 1\u003d 0\n2x - 4 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n2x^2 - 6x + 11 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n7x^2 - 56x + 49 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 7 and -7x + 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 7\u003d 0\n-7x + 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n7x^2 - 56x + 50 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-8x^2 - 16x + 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 3 and 8x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 3\u003d 0\n8x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-8x^2 - 16x + 25 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 - 6 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 1 and -6x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 1\u003d 0\n-6x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 - 2 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n-3x^2 + 18x + 21 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 7 and -3x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 7\u003d 0\n-3x - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-3x^2 + 18x + 30 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n15x^2 - 15x - 30 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x - 6 and 5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x - 6\u003d 0\n5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n15x^2 - 15x - 21 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 8", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 7x + 8 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 1 and x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 1\u003d 0\nx - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 7x + 12 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -9", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\nx^2 + 6x - 27 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 3 and x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 3\u003d 0\nx + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\nx^2 + 6x - 20 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n48x^2 - 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x - 8 and -6x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x - 8\u003d 0\n-6x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n48x^2 - 47 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 + 8x + 10 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 5 and -2x - 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 5\u003d 0\n-2x - 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 + 8x + 18 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -7", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 - 20x + 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x - 8 and -x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x - 8\u003d 0\n-x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 - 20x + 58 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -6", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 2x + 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 8 and x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 8\u003d 0\nx + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 2x + 53 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, 5", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\nx^2 + x - 30 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx + 6 and x - 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx + 6\u003d 0\nx - 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\nx^2 + x - 23 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 - 12x - 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n6x + 6 and x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n6x + 6\u003d 0\nx - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 - 12x - 14 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -4", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n6x^2 + 6x - 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x - 9 and 2x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x - 9\u003d 0\n2x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n6x^2 + 6x - 67 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\nx^2 + x - 2 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx + 2 and x - 1\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx + 2\u003d 0\nx - 1 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\nx^2 + x + 4 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-24x^2 + 48x + 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n8x + 8 and -3x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n8x + 8\u003d 0\n-3x + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-24x^2 + 48x + 74 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n4x^2 + 20x + 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-4x - 8 and -x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-4x - 8\u003d 0\n-x - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n4x^2 + 20x + 32 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n2x^2 - 4x - 16 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 8 and -x - 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 8\u003d 0\n-x - 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n2x^2 - 4x - 13 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n14x^2 - 14x - 28 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 4 and -7x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 4\u003d 0\n-7x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n14x^2 - 14x - 22 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n3x^2 + 15x + 18 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 3 and -3x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 3\u003d 0\n-3x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n3x^2 + 15x + 21 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-3x^2 + 12x - 9 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 3 and -3x + 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 3\u003d 0\n-3x + 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-3x^2 + 12x - 7 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6, 9", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 + 3x + 54 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx + 6 and -x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx + 6\u003d 0\n-x + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 + 3x + 57 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4, 5", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n2x^2 - 2x - 40 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x + 8 and x - 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x + 8\u003d 0\nx - 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n2x^2 - 2x - 31 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n64x^2 - 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x - 8 and -8x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x - 8\u003d 0\n-8x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n64x^2 - 56 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 - 24x - 36 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x + 6 and -2x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x + 6\u003d 0\n-2x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 - 24x - 29 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -3", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 + 4x + 48 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x + 8 and 2x + 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x + 8\u003d 0\n2x + 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 + 4x + 52 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-x^2 - 3x - 2 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 1 and x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 1\u003d 0\nx + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-x^2 - 3x \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 - 24x + 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 8 and 4x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 8\u003d 0\n4x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 - 24x + 65 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -4", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-18x^2 - 90x - 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n9x + 9 and -2x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n9x + 9\u003d 0\n-2x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-18x^2 - 90x - 68 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 + 32 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\nx - 4 and -2x - 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\nx - 4\u003d 0\n-2x - 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 + 35 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n21x^2 - 21 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x + 3 and 7x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x + 3\u003d 0\n7x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n21x^2 - 19 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-4x^2 + 4x + 8 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-4x - 4 and x - 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-4x - 4\u003d 0\nx - 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-4x^2 + 4x + 9 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n-2x^2 + 10x + 12 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 6 and 2x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 6\u003d 0\n2x + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-2x^2 + 10x + 20 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 4 from both sides of the equation.\n-30x^2 + 30 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-6x + 6 and 5x + 5\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-6x + 6\u003d 0\n5x + 5 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-30x^2 + 34 \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n-7x^2 + 63x - 56 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x + 8 and 7x - 7\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x + 8\u003d 0\n7x - 7 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-7x^2 + 63x - 51 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "Subtract 6 from both sides of the equation.\n-3x^2 + 3 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n3x + 3 and -x + 1\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n3x + 3\u003d 0\n-x + 1 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-3x^2 + 9 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-6x^2 + 54 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x - 9 and 2x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x - 9\u003d 0\n2x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-6x^2 + 55 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n-16x^2 - 80x - 64 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-2x - 8 and 8x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-2x - 8\u003d 0\n8x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-16x^2 - 80x - 63 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Subtract 2 from both sides of the equation.\n-30x^2 - 60x - 30 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n5x + 5 and -6x - 6\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n5x + 5\u003d 0\n-6x - 6 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-30x^2 - 60x - 28 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -1", "explanation": "Subtract 9 from both sides of the equation.\n9x^2 + 36x + 27 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-x - 3 and -9x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-x - 3\u003d 0\n-9x - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n9x^2 + 36x + 36 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -3", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n-27x^2 - 54x + 81 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-9x + 9 and 3x + 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-9x + 9\u003d 0\n3x + 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-27x^2 - 54x + 84 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Subtract 3 from both sides of the equation.\n8x^2 + 16x + 8 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-8x - 8 and -x - 1\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-8x - 8\u003d 0\n-x - 1 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n8x^2 + 16x + 11 \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Subtract 1 from both sides of the equation.\n8x^2 + 16x + 8 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n4x + 4 and 2x + 2\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n4x + 4\u003d 0\n2x + 2 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n8x^2 + 16x + 9 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, 2", "explanation": "Subtract 7 from both sides of the equation.\n-36x^2 + 108x - 72 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n9x - 9 and -4x + 8\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n9x - 9\u003d 0\n-4x + 8 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n-36x^2 + 108x - 65 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, 3", "explanation": "Subtract 5 from both sides of the equation.\n2x^2 - 14x + 24 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n2x - 8 and x - 3\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n2x - 8\u003d 0\nx - 3 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n2x^2 - 14x + 29 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -9", "explanation": "Subtract 8 from both sides of the equation.\n3x^2 + 24x - 27 \u003d 0.\nFactor out the polynomial into the two binomials.\n-3x + 3 and -x - 9\nFactor out any possible constants from each binomial.\nSet both binomials equal to 0\n-3x + 3\u003d 0\n-x - 9 \u003d 0\nSolve for x.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve by factoring:\n3x^2 + 24x - 19 \u003d 8", "type": "text"}
]}